你没事吧?
You okay?
没事  只是被横梁卡住
Yeah, I just got clipped with a beam.
你们两个是不是脑袋短路了?
What the hell do you two think you were doing?
我们好像听见那儿有人
We thought we heard someone in there.
未经许可你不能进去
You never go in without authorization.
队长 都怪我 Amy只是跟我进去
Captain, this is all me.Amy just followed me in.
你去年烧伤还觉得不过瘾  是吧?
So torching your ass last year wasn't enough, huh?
别总想着逞英雄  小心害死自己
You need to stop trying to prove how ,tough you are before you get yourself killed.
是 长官
Yes, sir.
到医护人员那检查一下
Go have the paramedics look you over.
过来 Derek 把这个梯子升到二层
Come on, derek, let's get this ,ladder to the second story.
快点
Let's go.
Derek!
怎么了?
What's happening?
我...好冷
I'M...freezing.
我很好
I'm fine.
急救医生可不这么认为
Er docs don't think so.
你体温波动就像过山车一样
Your temperature's been going up ,and down like a roller coaster.
这些植皮多久了?
How old are these skin grafts?
最后一次手术大约六个月前
Last one was about six months ago.
得做些检查 ,我还要和House医生商量一下
Gonna run some tests,and we'll get ,a consult with dr. House.
过会儿就没事了
I'll be fine.
一切都要听医生的  知道吗?
You'll be doing what the doctors say.,Got it?
我过会儿再来
I'll check in later.
嗨
Hey.
你昨晚替我掩饰的那些话
The way you covered for me last night.
他是我哥哥
He's my brother.
对付他就得争取主动
I know how to eat it from him.
我下班再来  好吗?
I'm gonna stop after my shift, okay?
好的
Yeah.
那好
Okay.
House医生在哪?
So where is this dr. House?
辩论场上
Speaking engagement.
无罪
Not guilty.
非法获取精神类药物的指控
And on the charge of gaining control of
你如何辩护?
said medication by fraud, how do you plead?
无罪
Not guilty.
那好
Very well.
初步聆讯定于19号上午10点
Preliminary hearing is set for ,the 19th at 10:00 am,
那时我再确定
at which time I'll determine whether
是否有足够的证据进入庭审
there's enough evidence to proceed to trial.
下一案件 公诉Williams,控二级攻击罪
Next case on the calendar,people V. Williams,charged assault for second degree
你想过去找他谈?
You're gonna go talk to him?
我只想问他在哪里做的发型
I was just gonna ask him where he gets his hair cut.
他们有你签名的药房记录
They have your signature in a prescription log,
保安监控录像
a security camera video,
还有一个宣过誓的药剂师的证词
and a pharmacist's sworn statement saying
说你偷拿死者的药
you stole the dead guy's pills.
足够判你十年
You're already looking at ten years.
你还想再加上一条威胁证人的罪名?
You want to add witness intimidating charge?
那就去吧
Go ahead.
去问他的发型
Ask him about his hair.
一年前他全身54%的面积三度烧伤
He suffered third degree burns over ,54% of his body a year ago
昨晚由于失去方向感和颤抖,被送进急救室
and arrived in the er last night ,disoriented and shivering.
到目前的12个小时里他的体温,徘徊于96到102度之间
For 12 hours his temperature was,bouncing between 96 and 102.
为什么不质疑取证程序?
Why don't you contest the search ,of the pharmacy records?
你可以辩称他违反医患保密规定
Yeah, you could argue it violated ,doctor-patient confidentiality.
问题是他当时不是病人也非医生
Except he wasn't the patient or the doctor.
只是个从病人和医生那里偷药的人
He was the guy who stole from ,the patient and the doctor.
这是两个礼拜以来他,第三次失去方向感了
This was the third time he had been ,disoriented in the last two weeks.
冲进烟雾弥漫着大火的房子里,本来就会有点头晕
Running into smoke-filled burning buildings ,can be a bit disorienting.
幸运的事  这都可以治
Fortunately, I have the cure.
别再进火场
Stop doing it.
他现在不在着火的房子里了,可他还是不停颤抖
He's not in a burning building anymore,,and he's still shivering.
下丘脑的肿瘤可能导致体温波动
A hypothalamic tumor could cause ,a vacillating temperature.
可能急救室里哪个粗心的护士
So could er nurses who are too busy to notice
没注意病人喜欢,热咖啡和冰汽水一起喝
that a patient likes both hot coffee and cold sodas.
丙肝 肺结核和爱滋病以及莱姆病,都呈阴性 毒理检测也是
He tested negative for hep c,tb, hiv, ,lyme,and his tox screen's clean.
看来你是没注意  我没心情跳舞
In case you hadn't noticed,,not exactly in the mood to dance.
我不是邀请你跳舞,我是提醒你要尽职工作
I'm not asking you to dance.,I asking you to do your job.
心电图显示心律不齐
Ekg showed arrhythmia.
可能只是轻微的心脏病
Probably just a mild heart attack.
没有胸部痛感
No chest pain.
而且吸入烟雾就能导致心律不齐
And smoke inhalation already ,explains the arrhythmia.
这人在烧伤病房待了6个月,做了一系列手术
The guy was in the burn unit for six months ,and had multiple surgeries.
可能是院内感染 MRSA,(耐甲氧西林金黄色葡萄球菌)
Could be a hospital-acquired infection.,Maybe mrsa
我同意
Works for me.
做个全血培养  给他用抗生素
Draw blood cultures.Start him on antibiotics.
万古霉素加上,广谱抗革兰氏阴性菌的
Vancomycin plus broad gram negative coverage.
如果你想看我的监狱纹身,我还没设计好
If you called to see the design ,for my prison tats,they're still in r&D.
你得和Tritter谈谈
You need to talk to tritter.
我的律师不是这么说的
Not according to my lawyer.
律师可没本事说服检查官取消案子,而Tritter可以
Your lawyer isn't gonna be able to get the da ,to the drop the case.Tritter caN.
是啊 还有什么Tritter做不到的?
Yeah, you know what else tritter can do?
你这是做给谁看?
You are not impressing anyone.
或许这是你所谓的原则
You may call yourself principled,
但你实际上是个一根筋到底的,不谙世事的白痴
but what you really are is stubborn,adolescent idiot.
- 这可不是他的错,- 我又不是那个...
- This isn't his fault. ,- I'm not the one--
是你往他直肠里塞体温计
you used the rectal thermometer on him.
也是你在该道歉的时候羞辱了他
You insulted him instead of apologizing.
还是你 居然当着他的面磕药
You flaunted your drug use in his face.
最后还拒绝了他的提议
And you refused to accept a deal--
我接受了协议...
I accepted the deaL.
偷拿死者的药之后
Not until after you stole a dead guy's pills.
没证据
Allegedly.
Tritter一直都给你留一条活路
Tritter has been opening doors ,for you every step of the way,
而你却一再错过
and you keep slamming them shut.
他现在不会再留情了 House
There are no more openings to give, house.
如果你不想坐牢 ,只能看你的本事了
If you want to stay out of prison,,you gotta make one for yourself.
这是维柯丁
It's vicodin.
吃了你的状态会好点
You function better on it.
找他谈谈
Talk to him.
MRSA是种入院的患者常感染的病菌
Mrsa's a bacteria that often ,infects hospital patients.
烧伤导致皮肉暴露在外,更容易感染病菌
The burns on your chest and arm exposed ,raw flesh that made youa wide open target.
但是抗生素会消灭它们 对吗?
But the antibiotics will take care of it, right?
那得看菌株
Depends on what strainit is.
做完血液培养我们才能确定
We'll know more once weget the results ,back from these cultures.
那么 这个...
So this...
叫做MRSA的病菌...
mrsa thing...
会不会使我看到的东西都是蓝色的?
would it make everything look blue?
他看见的全是蓝色
He's seeing blue.
你哪来的处方?
Who'd you get the scrip from?
Cuddy.
Cuddy
你想知道我给她什么了吗?
You want to know what I gave her?
MRSA不会影响他的视觉颜色分辨
Mrsa wouldn't change his ocular palette.
重金属中毒能使视觉颜色发生改变,特别是铊
Heavy metal poisoning could cause ,vision changes,particularly thallium.
如果是铊中毒,他会脱发
If it was thallium,he'd be losing his hair.
或许是更年期呢
So maybe it's menopause.
他才28岁
He's 28 years old.
对啊 年纪才是奇怪之处,男人有更年期不奇怪
Yes, his age is the reason it's weird ,that a man has menopause.
男性更年期
Male menopause.
雌激素增高 睾丸激素降低
High estrogen,low testosterone.
会导致体温波动 失去方向感
Explains the temperature swings,disorientation.
内分泌情况就像女性更年期
Endocrinologically similar to female menopause
只差没有阴道和不打麻将
but without the vaginas and mah-jongg tiles.
男性更年期无法解释视觉蓝色
Male menopause doesn't explain the blue vision.
视觉蓝色不是症状,而是伟哥的副作用
The blue vision isn't a symptom, ,it's a side effect of viagra.
说明书上写着呢
It's right there on the label.
因为我是医生 所以我知道,我不用伟哥
Which I have no reason to have read ,except that I'm a doctor.
他没服用伟哥
He's not taking viagra.
你的意思是他没对你说服用过伟哥
You mean he didn't tell you he was taking viagra.
不管他病的多重 相信我
I don't care how sick he is, trust me.
他绝对不会放弃找女人的
He still thinks he's got a shot.
更年期综合症导致体温波动和疲软
Menopause causes temperature swings, limpness.
疲软就依赖药物 药物导致视觉蓝色
Limpness causes pills,pills cause the blues.
他没出现其他早衰的症状
He's presenting no other signs of premature aging.
早衰并不是唯一的诱因
Aging's not the only cause.
你说过他全身54%的面积烧伤
You said that's he got burns on 54% of his body.
你敢肯定那1%没烧到?
Sure it's not 55%?
生殖器烧伤可能导致睾丸受损
Burns to his genitals could cause testicular trauma.
那就使他需要...
Which in turn could cause?
做个荷尔蒙检测
Run a hormone panel.
能确诊的话就给他注射一大管睾丸激素,然后让他回家
Comes back positive,pump him full ,of testosterone and send him home.
别再跟着我了
And stop following me.
幸亏我父母不在了
Thank god my parents are dead.
如果我父亲知道我有更年期了,我真活不下去了
If the old man had heard I had menopause,I'd never live it down.
这没什么可羞耻的
It's nothing to be ashamed of.
一旦这些睾丸激素在体内溶解,你会恢复的和以前一样
Once these testosterone pellets dissolve,your system will be back to normal.
是啊 但在那之前,我会像个老妇女
Yeah, but till then I'm an old lady.
我进来没事吧?
Okay to come in?
不是MRSA
It's not mrsa.
他不用再隔离了
He's not being isolated anymore.
只要不是穿白大褂的都欢迎
Anyone not in a white coat is welcome.
你看起来不错,感觉如何?
You're looking better.,How you feeling?
我很好
I'm good.
除了要补充些荷尔蒙
Turns out I got some hormone thing.
他们正在注射
They're fixing it right now.
你没事吧?
You okay?
是的 我想是的  只是-
Yeah, I think so.I just--uhh!
Derek 感到疼吗?
Derek, you in pain?
把针管拔掉
You need to get these out.
- 等一下 怎么了?,- 快拔掉
- Hold on.What's wrong? ,- Get these out.
- 怎么回事?,- 像是过敏
- What's going on? ,- Looks like an allergic reaction.
Derek 坚持住 ,我们给你些抗过敏的药物
Derek, hold on, ,we're gonna get you something to stop it.
- 不 快拔掉,- 你冷静点
- No, just take 'em out! ,- You gotta calm down.
拔掉! Derek!
Get 'em out!Derek!
Derek 放开她!
Derek, let her go!
我需要2毫克劳拉西泮 静脉注射
I need two milligrams iv lorazepam stat!
快拔掉
Get 'em out!
投诉部门在走廊对面
Complaint department's across the hall.
我很忙
I'm busy.
我猜你是想投诉,我之前的做法有失公允
Can I just assume that you told me ,how unfair I'm being and--
对不起
I'm sorry.
随便从傲慢或是精神错乱,这样的形容词里挑一个
You could throw a dart at all ,the adjectives between arrogant
肯定都符合我
and unhinged and I'm sure ,you'd hit one that describes me.
我那个德行是有原因的
There's a reason I operate that way.
我生活在病痛中
I live in pain.
平时的疼只不过是难耐
Pain that on good days is merely intolerable,
疼的厉害的时候 整个人都没了生气
but on bad ones will suck ,the life force right out of you.
我这么做不太对
Doesn't mean that I've handled this right.
实际上... 我错了
Actually...means I was wrong.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我明白道歉的话
I know that couldn't have been...
从你嘴里说出很不容易
easy for you to say.
哪怕你心里并无歉意
Even if you don't mean a word of it.
对不起
I'm sorry.
你可以让我上测慌仪
You can hook me up to a damn polygraph.
我想测谎仪也会被你骗过
And I'm sure you'd pass.
重要的是 我不在乎你的言辞
The thing is, I've never been interested ,in what you have to say.
而是在乎你的行动
All I care about is what you do.
我们听证会见
I'll see you at the hearing.
不是药物影响
it wasn't the medicine.
病菌和过敏检测均呈阴性
Contamination and allergy tests ,both came back negative.
没发现肺部血栓
There was nothing to suggest a pulmonary embolism.
动态心电图结果是心动过速造成的
And his ekg showed the expected tachycardia ,from the exertion of the attack.
而且我没事  多谢关心
And I'm fine by the way,thanks for asking.
症状发作太快可能有神经系统病变
aggression comes on that fast,it's gotta have a neurologic basis.
我们该做个CT排除垂体肿瘤,腰椎穿刺排除脑膜炎
We should do a ctfor a frontal lobe tumor ,and an lp for meningitis.
很好
Great.
安排检查
Have at it.
这样就完了?
That's it?
不再质疑我们的诊断?,不再挖苦我们?
No challenging our theory?,No tearing us down?
没必要
No need.
你们做的很好
You've got it under control.
你要去哪里?
Where are you going?
上楼
Upstairs this time.
去做什么?
To do what?
进康复中心
Check myself into rehab.
Tritter又和你达成一项协议?
did tritter offer you another deal?
没有 都是我的主意
Nope.This is all me.
没有拍拍背 说些鼓励的话?
So, no slaps on the back,encouraging words?
我们只是想知道到底怎么回事?
We're just trying to understand what this is.
希望是脱瘾反应
I hope it's me detoxing.
否则我昨晚弄脏了一套,那么好的内衣就太不值了
Otherwise I soiled a perfectly good pair ,of underwear last night for nothing.
那这回来真的?
So this is for real?
不是做样子给Tritter看?
It's not just a show for tritter?
当然是做样子给Tritter看
Absolutely it's a show for tritter.
还有法官
And the judge.
做样子就是要真做
Unfortunately,unless it's real,,there is no show.
嘿 要是对我的案子没帮助,那至少
Hey, if it doesn't help my case,then at least
我能神志清醒地去监狱
I can go to prison with heightened senses.
享受我的放风时间
All the better to enjoy my strolls around the yard.
时间到了 开始社团活动
Time's up.Group's starting.
我得检查一下这堆东西
Gonna need to check that stuff.
我要是带领大批病人造反的话,首先要解决的就是这个伏地魔
When I lead the big patient rebellion,,voldemort here is first to go.
CT检查正常 没有垂体肿瘤
Ct was normal.No frontal lobe tumor.
腰穿也没查出脑膜炎,我们又回到原点了
Lp was negativefor meningitis.,We're back to square one.
那血管病变呢?
What about something vascular?
结节性多动脉炎?
Polyarterit is nodosa?
脑部损伤CT上应该能看出来
Brain lesions would've shown up on the ct
军团病可以解释寒战和体温波动
legionnaire's explains the chills and temperature.
影响精神状态导致具有攻击性
Altered mental status causes the aggression.
我们忽略了呼吸问题
We would've seen respiratory problems.
我们是在乱打乱撞
We're throwing darts.
我们得去问House
We need to go to house.
我们要自己解决
We need to deal with this ourselves.
他能安排出时间,Derek始终是他的病人
He can make the time.,Derek's still his patient.
等他来确诊病人可能都不行了
The man's life as he knows it could be over.
我们还是别去找他了
I think you of all people would ,want to cut him some slack.
我们救的是个为了营救陌生人,而冒险跑进大火的人
We're treating a man who runs into ,burning buildings for perfect strangers.
他的伤不是自己的错
He didn't ask for what's happening to him.
哪像House什么都是自找的
House did everything to himself.
别人已经够对他手下留情的了
He's been cut more than enough slack.
目前 House有更重要的事要做
Right now, house has more important ,things to deal with.
我头一次见他是在几个月前
It was the first time I'd seen him in months.
我以为他会挽住我说他理解我
I guess I was hoping he'd put his arms ,around me and tell me he understood.
但是他却说不能原谅我
But he said he wasn't ready to forgive me.
他也许永远不会
he may never be ready.
你能做的只有一件事
You're doing the only thing you can do.
尽力
You're trying.
你呢? Greg?
How about you, greg?
想通该如何与你身边的人相处了吗?
You thought about how to fix things ,with people in your life?
没那个必要
No need.
我身边的人从来不指望我什么
People in my life have no expectations of me.
这让我们都解脱
Makes all our lives easier.
显然不是
Apparently not.
- 康复的第一阶段,- 是承认我有问题
- The first step in recovery--,- is admitting I have a problem.
明摆着 否则我也不会到这来
I've obviously done that,or I wouldn't be here.
第二阶段我也同意
I've even embraced step two.
承认这个世界上有超越凡人的力量
I've accepted that there is a higher power.
也许不一定叫上帝,那个巨人Andre(著名摔角手)就够强大了
Maybe not a god perse,,but that andre the giant guyw as powerful.
我有抵触的是第三步
Where I start to butt up ,against it is step three
放弃自己的意志  臣服于超然力量
surrendering my will to this higher power.
虽然Andre做了鬼也跟着我,但是我的自由意志
I'm sure andre's ghost has my back ,and all,but my free will?
从来不会丢开
I never leave home without it.
就像你的药
Kind of like your pills.
如果你自己能戒得掉,你也不会来这里
If you could do this on your own,,I assume you wouldn't be here.
是的
True.
每人都会说谎
Everybody lies.
他的毒理检测
His tox screen.
每次都是阴性
It's been clean every time.
正是
Exactly.
那不可能 ,大面积的植皮肯定疼的要命
It shouldn't bE.He's had extensive skin grafts,which hurt like hell.
并不是人人都像House,有些人不用药物也能忍住
Not everybody's house.People can handle ,pain without medication.
但他们还是疼啊
But they do have pain.
这个人担心失业,疼却不说
This guy's worried about losing his job,so he's hiding the pain.
我们查出痛处或许能找到问题所在
We find out where the pain is,maybe we find out where the problem is.
或是他根本感觉不到疼
Or he doesn't feel pain.
不管何种解释 一定有事
Either way,it's something.
什么时候?
When?
2分钟前 脉搏137  呼吸42
Two minutes ago.Pulse is 137.,Respiration 42.
他刚才还挺好 正在讲笑话
He was fine.He was just telling me a joke.
让她离开这
Get her out of here.
肺部没有积水
No fluid in his lungs.
血氧饱和度85 严重缺氧,我们准备插管
O2 set's 85.He's hypoxic.,We're gonna have to intubate.
不是肺部,心电图ST段升高
It's not his lungs.,He's got marked s-t elevation.
他心脏病发作
He's having a heart attack.
选个颜色
Pick a color.
服药时间
Medication time.
你是阴天里的一束阳光
You are a ray of sunshine on a cloudy day.
他稳定了
He's stable.
不会稳定太久
Won't stay that way.
他的血检报告显示,肌肉钙蛋白和心肌酶含量上升
His blood tests show troponins and ckmb up.
Chase是对的 他胸部疼痛没说
Chase was right.He was hiding chest pain.
他的心脏病发作了好几次
He's been having a whole series of heart attacks.
心脏病不会让人伸手想掐死某人
Heart attacks can't cause you to ,reach out and choke someone.
脑部缺氧会让人产生幻觉
Lack of oxygen to the brain causes disorientation.
大量的肾上腺素导致情绪激动
Increased adrenaline causes rage.
更重要的问题是,什么导致心脏病?
More important question is,,what caused the attacks?
你去哪?
Where you going?
去见House
To see house.
我们有个28岁动脉血管正常的病人
We have a 28-year-old with clean arteries,
没有心脏的瓣膜畸形,却患有多种心脏病
no valvular abnormalities having multiple attacks.
我可不会坐等另一种心脏病发作
I'm not gonna wait for chase to ,give us another breakthrough.
或许我们该回去
Maybe we should go.
我们还没讨论出结果
We don't have an answer yet.
顺便说一句 我很好多谢关心
I'm fine by the way,thanks for asking.
谁想出的用丁丙诺啡来戒除维柯丁,真该挨枪子
Whoever came up with buprenorphine to ,wean off vicodin should be shot.
还要刺瞎他的眼睛
Then stabbed in the eye.
某人是不是该换一换我的药了!
Think someone needs to adjust my meds!
心脏没有炎症和...
The heart shows no signs of inflammation or
这种心脏病不是内源的
the cause of the heart attacks isn't internal.
是外源的  受环境影响
It must be external,something environmental.
这几次发作都不在同一个地方
None of the attacks happened in the same place.
还是有共同点
Still must be something in common.
第一次在着火的公寓大楼
First one happenedin an apartment building fire.
火 水 烟 氧气  面罩
Fire, water, smoke,oxygen masks.
第二次和第三次发生在这儿
And the second and third ones happened here.
没火没水也没烟
There's no fire,no water, no smoke.
他穿的衣服也不同,身体也清洗过了
His clothes are all different.,He'd been cleaned.
不要光想着物 还有人
That's the what'S.How about the who's?
- 他的拍档Amy三次发作都在场 但是,- 还有其他人,吗?
His partner amy was at all three attacks, ,but--anyone else?
人不会引发心脏病
People don't cause heart attacks.
哦 你该想想怎么证明我是错的
Well, you should be worried about proving me wrong.
amy?
Amy?
请跟我来?
Would you come with me, please?
我弟弟情况有变?
Anything new on my brother?
现在还不确定 ,能跟我来一下吗?
We're not quite sure yet.,Could you come with me?
当然
Yeah.
这是为什么?
What's this all about?
我不知道
I don't know.
他们想和我们一起谈谈
They wanted to talk to us together.
Derek!
House是对的
House was right.
我不明白
I don't get it.
我怎么会引发他的心脏病?
How can I be causing his heart attacks?
或学你携带了触发的物质
You may be carrying an agent that triggered them.
任何东西都可能,霉菌孢子 有毒植物碎屑
It could be anything.,Mold spores,poisonous plant residue,
从火场带来的一些东西
something you picked up at a fire site.
除非我们找到这种物质,否则不能让你接近Derek
Until we identy the agent,,we can't allow you near derek.
我不敢相信我害他成这样
I can't believe that I'm doing this to him.
你不必责备自己
You can't blame yourself for this.
你知道他为什么会植皮吗?
You know how he got those skin grafts?
他在火场被烧伤
He was trapped in a fire.
我们在一幢办公大楼清理火灾现场
We were clearing rooms in an office building fire,
天花板忽然塌了
and the ceiling collapsed.
把我困在房间内
And it cut me off from the rest of the group.
我大声说自己没事
And I kept yelling that I was fine,
但是Derek等不及救援队来清理残骸
but derek refused to wait for ,the team to clear the debris,
他动身寻找其他进入点
so he took off looking for another access point.
被复燃火烧伤
He got caught in a back draft.
差点因为我而送命
He almost died because of me once.
这次又是因为我
And now it's happening again.
你又不是我妈妈
You're not my mom.
不用老来看我
You don't have to keep checking up on me.
最近如何?
How you doing?
还不错
Not bad.
我刚意识到自己在这里权势尽失
Considering I've just learned ,I'm completely powerless
看到这整个楼区了吗?
see this big fancy wing?
之所以存在就是因为能帮助戒毒
It was built because this program works.
逻辑错误
Faulty logic.
这个楼区之所以存在,是因为出钱的人认为能帮助戒毒
This big fancy wing exists because ,some people with money think that it works.
他们以为有钱什么都能买
They want to believe they can buy a better world.
这简直就是绝望中的幻想
This is nothing short of idealized despair.
还让其他人也沉浸在这里面
Let other people wallow in it.
我不知道那是什么意思
I don't even know what that means.
这什么都不是
None of this means anything.
只是空喊口号和陈词滥调
It's just nonsensicals logans and platitudes.
意思是耐心点 不是马上见效
Meaning takes time.It takes work.
你以为我在干吗?
What do you think I've been doing?
你才来这里两天
You've been here for two days.
就大谈沉浸在这里
Talk about wallowing in it.
我们都清楚
We all get it.
我知道你要忍受多少痛苦
We know how much pain you have.
你就是来面对这种痛苦,开始新生活的
You're here to deal with that ,and get on with your life.
是啊
Right.
我应该和一个将死的病人搞外遇,然后搬去酒店住
I should have an affair with a dying patient ,and move into a hotel.
你是懦夫 House
You're a coward, house.
你总挑别人的毛病,因为你害怕面对自我
You find fault in everybody,because ,you're afraid to look at yourself.
多谢
Thanks.
正愁想不出什么陈词滥调
I was running short on platitudes.
你可以走了
You can leave now.
我们检测了Amy身上的十几种物质
We tested amy for about a dozen different agents,
都不是诱因
but they all came back negative.
所以她不是诱因
So she's not causing the attacks.
Derek...  你是不是很爱她?
Derek...are you in love with her?
难道有什么关系吗?
What does that have to do with anything?
Amy告诉我你要植皮的原因了
Amy told me how you got those skin grafts.
我知道你很照顾她
And the way you're always watching out for her.
也看见你看她的眼神
And I see the way you look at her.
你告诉过她吗?
Have you told her how you feel?
她有个六岁大的女儿
She has a six-year-old daughter.
当妈妈照样能恋爱
Women with daughters can still fall in love.
我知道
I know.
因为她跟我哥哥相爱了
Because she did.With my brother.
他们订婚了
They're engaged.
伤心综合症
broken heart syndrome.
他爱上一个人 却受着折磨
He's in love,and it's killing him.
我以为只有八十岁的寡妇才会酱紫
Thought that only happened to 80-year-old widows.
多亏了他的绝经期还有雌激素水平 ,基本上他就是一个老太太
Thanks to his menopause and estrogen level ,he basically is an old woman.
Bhs是一种对情感体验的剧烈身体反映
Bhs is an acute physical response ,to an emotional experience.
压力触发了儿茶酚胺的大量产生
Stress triggers a flood of catecholamines
那是一种很普遍的疲劳原发性心肌症,不是心脏病发作
that's a plain old stress cardiomyopathy,not a heart attack.
但是如果你太担心因为治病
But if you're too worried about losing your job
失去你的工作 他们就会转变成 ,全方位的心脏病发作
to get it treated,they can devolve ,into full-on heart attacks.
你觉得在amy订婚的时候发生,这只是一种巧合么
You think it's a coincidence this ,started when amy got engaged?
不 我不觉得
No, I don'T.
现在已经知道为什么了,剩下要做的就是如何去解决
But now that you know the why,what are you gonna do to stop the how?
我们已经给他注射了β-受体阻滞药 ,和硝化甘油 没有效果
We already put him on beta blockers ,and nitroglycerine,no effect.
我们需要给他用抗抑郁剂
We need to put him on anti-depressants.
除非你是正确的
Not if you're right.
抗抑郁剂会抑制 ,他的自主神经系统
Anti-depressants would inhibit ,his autonomic nervous system
那只会加速他的心脏病发作
which would only speed up the heart attacks.
我们可以给他三丙基硫脲嘧啶,(抗甲亢,心绞痛或充血性心力衰竭等的药物)
We could trypropyl thiouracil.
降低他的新陈代谢速度
Slow down his metabolic rate.
甲状腺反映只会让心脏变得更脆弱
Thyroid effect would only weaken the heart.
那唯一的方法只有用血液稀释剂了
The only other optionis blood thinners.
这又不是一个动脉脆弱的肥仔
This is not a fat guy with plaque-filled ,arteries and a swollen heart.
是他的大脑企图杀死心脏
He's a guy whose brain is trying to his heart.
那就去给他找个女朋友 让他开心点
So buy him a girlfriend.Make him happy.
那只是你眼里的快乐罢了
That might make you happy.
唯一能让他开心的只有amy
The only thing that'll make him happy is amy.
那就让他离她远点就好了
So keep him away from her.
每次她走进病房他就会心肌梗塞
He has a myocardial infarction every time ,she walks in the room.
如果我们告诉他以后再也见不到她,你觉得他的心脏会怎么样
What do you think will happen to his heart ,when we tell him he can never see her again?
他需要一个心理医生
he needs a shrink.
chase的意见跟以往一样出色
Chase's idea is as good as any.
因为要做脑子电击治疗 ,而且还要把amy赶走
Because short of fryingh is brain ,and wiping amy out,
他会崩溃的
he's screwed.
找cuddy
We need cuddy.
做什么
Why?
这样你就可以告诉她 为什么,你要去油炸一个男人的脑子
So you can tell her why you need to ,fry a guy's brain.
他的心脏有问题,而你要电击他的脑子
The guy's heart isn't working,and you want to shock his brain.
电击疗法是把amy从他记忆里抹去的唯一办法
Electroshock therapy is the only way ,to erase his memories of amy
而且可以停止大脑对心脏的攻击
and stop the brain's chemical attack on the heart.
现在又不是1940年 ,这种病症可以通过使用抗抑郁剂控制
This is 1940.The problem can be ,controlled with anti-depressants.
Cameron?
Cameron
抗抑郁剂会抑制他的,自主神经系统 加速攻击
Anti-depressants would inhibit his ,autonomic nervous system,speed up the attacks.
Lmno 丙基硫尿嘧啶 ,血液稀释剂没有一样起作用
Lmno, ptu, blood thinners,none of ,them will solve this problem.
这个人脑子里自导自演了一场浪漫滑稽剧
The man's got a real-life harlequin romance in his head.
只能动用1940年的办法
We're gonna pull out the 1940 playbook.
双面电极,高强度正弦波刺激
Bilateral electrodes,,high stimulus sine-wave intensity,
把刻度一直拨到11
turning that dial all the way to 11.
基本的脑部化学反应
It's basic brain chemistry.
我们打断蛋白质合成,改变神经传递系统
We interrupt protein synthesis,,altering the neuro transmitter system.
最终结果 没记忆 没amy 没问题
End results: No memories,no amy,no problem.
好吧
Go ahead.
听到这位女士说的了 去把他插上电
You heard the lady.Go plug him in.
我是不是真的那么可悲
Am I really that pathetic?
你在说些什么
What are you talking about?
如果我选择电击疗法
If I had pitche delectroshock therapy
在任何一个别的时候治疗伤心综合征
as a cure for broken heart syndrome any other time,
你肯定会坚持先用一百种没用的方法去治疗
you'd have dug in and maybe try ,a hundred other useless things first.
所以要不然是你真的开始信任我
So either you're actually beginning to trust me,
或者只是出于同情
or you just feel sorry for me.
你的想法很有道理
You presented a reasonable argument.
你很清醒 一点也不冲动
You were clear-headed and non-impulsive about it.
没有再用过白痴这个词
Never once used the word "moron."
复健有效果了 house
The rehab's working, house.
你仍有能力完成基本的日常生活,象走路 讲话 系鞋带
you'll still be able to perform routine ,functions like walking, talking,tying your shoes.
治疗的目标是扣带皮层(位于扣带回的大脑皮层)
The treatment targets the anterior cingulate cortex.
这只会影响到你经历过的记忆
It should only affect your experiential memories.
那我的父母 我的童年呢
So my parents?My childhood?
如果起作用了 你会忘记他们
If this works,you won't remember them.
还有你的消防员训练
Or your fire fighting training.
还有 amy
And amy.
你介意吗
Are you okay with that?
我不会想她的 对么
I wouldn't miss her,right?
告诉amy你的感觉,因为如果她真的爱你
Tell amy how you feel,because if she loves you
不 我不会对她这么做
no.I won't do that to her.
也不会对我哥哥这么做
Or to my brother.
你实际上为了保守这个秘密,毁掉了自己
You're effectively killing ,who you are just to keep this secret.
她并不爱我
She doesn't love me.
毛毛虫?
Caterpillar?
患有溃疡性结肠炎的肠道
Lower intestine  with ulcerative colitis.
你闯进艺术治疗课教室来找刺激?
You crash art therapy classes ,just for the adrenaline rush?
Cuddy一定要我亲眼来看下你的状况
Cuddy wouldn't get off the phone
才肯挂下电话
until I promised I'd come and see for myself.
我得承认 我没料到你这一招
I gotta admit,this move I did not expect.
好吧 别跟别人说 ,宣传小册子上的那些微笑面孔
Well, don't tell anyone,but the photos of ,smiling people in the brochure
只是市场营销手段
is just marketing.
不管怎样 你的确在努力
Well, you're obviously making an effort.
所以我假设下一步我要...
So i suppose the next step is for me to...
跟地方检察官谈谈
talk to the da.
而你并无此意
Which you have no intention of doing.
对
No.
所以语言没有意义 行动没有意义,还他X的剩下什么
So words mean nothing,actions mean nothing.,What the hell is left?
你这狗娘养的
You son of a bitch!
你的承诺呢 还有你的行动
What about your words?Your actions?
"要帮House改邪归正"
"Gotta get house cleaned up.
"羞辱一下他"
Gotta get him to show some humility."
但是当真正要做些什么的时候
But when it comes to actually doing something,
你唯一证实的就是
you've proved that all you care about
你只是想耍弄一个不想拍你马屁的人
is bitch-slapping a guy ,who refused to kiss your ass.
你会信任一个瘾君子吗
You ever trust an addict?
曾经以好意揣测过他们吗?
You ever give one the benefit of the doubt?
又有多少次 你洞穿他们的谎言?
How many times did it work out for you
是是 我懂你的意思了
yeah, yeah, yeah, I get it.
你被你的父母 妻子 同事给毁了
So you were screwed over by your wife,,your mother, your partner.
但你仍然发圣诞卡给他们表示关心
But you keep sending them christmas cards
却把你的怨气发泄到其他人身上!
while you take it out on everyone else.
不再送圣诞卡了
No more christmas cards.
我现在明白了
No, I learned...
象你这种人  不仅说话
people like you...
就算是行动也是假的
even your actions lie.
我很害怕
I'm scared.
我明白
I know.
我会帮你注射肌肉迟缓剂以防止抽筋
I'm gonna give you a muscle relaxant ,so your body doesn't convulse.
倒数计时
Count backwards from ten.
10...
9...
8...
7...
开始
go.
你叫什么
what's your name?
Derek.
Derek
心跳正常
Heart sounds good.
你知道我们在哪座城市吗
Do you know what city we're in?
不知道
No.
你介意有人来探望下你吗
Would you be okay with a couple of visitors?
是我 Brock
Derek, it's--it's me.Brock.
你哥哥 你出院后我会来照顾你
I'm your brother,and when you get out of here,you'll be staying with me.
我是 amy
I'm amy.
你的朋友
I'm your friend.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
你们我一个也不认识
But I don't remember either of you.
已经完成4次电击治疗
we've give him four rounds of electroshock.
电负荷让他的嗓音偏高,但心电图 血压都一切正常
The charge made his voice a little higher,,but the ekg and bpare good.
很好
Good.
明天早上会给他最后一次电击治疗
We're gonna give him his last round in the morning,
然后去参加你的听证
then be in court for your hearing.
谢谢
Thanks.
我要留在这里
I'm gonna stay here.
监控derek的病情
Monitor derek.
谢谢报告最新病情
Thanks for the update.
我的下一位悼念者来了
My next condolence callis arriving.
明天见
I'll see you guys tomorrow.
给你带了点东西
I got you something.
不错
Nice.
我猜这能给法官留下好点的印象
I figured it might help make a ,good impression on the judge.
没好到那么不错
It's not that nice.
我没任何理由责怪你
I had no business blaming you for any of this.
我知道你只是想帮我
I know you were just trying to help me.
保护我 尽朋友的义务
Protect me.That's what friends do.
你是在道歉吗?
Is this an apology?
康复步骤要求的
Part of the program.
你不喜欢 我现在就可以停止
You don't like it,I can stop.
没有
Not at all.
只是...不太习惯
It's just so...unfamiliar.
请继续
Please, keep going.
他看起来很困惑
He looks lost.
这需要一定的时间来调整
It's gonna take him a while.
Brock 去加班了
Brock's pulling a double shift.
他不忍心看他这个样子
He can't stand to see him this way.
Derek 很需要他做支柱
Derek's gonna need him, amy.
我知道在婚礼前遇到这种事会很让人困扰
I know the timing isn't great ,with a wedding coming up.
什么婚礼
What wedding?
你和brock的婚礼
Yours.You and brock.
我们没准备结婚
We're not getting married.
我们甚至没在约会
We don't even date.
为什么你觉得我们打算结婚
Why would you think we're getting married?
当你第一次劝说House医生,去康复中心治疗的时候 他的反应是什么
When you first offered dr. House the chance ,to check into drug rehab,how did he respond?
他让我滚出他的办公室
He told me to get ou tof his office.
我警告了他...
I warned him that...
这么做可能会吊销医疗执照并坐牢
he could end up in prison and ,lose his medical license.
也许他有担心过 但肯定没表现出来
If he was concerned,he didn't show it.
于是你继续开展了调查
so you continued your investigation.
是的 我追踪到了医院的药房
Yes, which is what lead me to the hospital pharmacy.
把它关了
Turn it off.
我说过别在审判时打电话给我
I thought I told you never to call me ,when I'm on trial.
那些记忆都是虚构的,我们的电击治疗白费了
The memories were false.,We fried his brain for nothing.
致命的病症仍然存在
Whatever was killing him before is still there.
已经做了核磁共振
We did an mri.
发现脑皮层动脉轻微缺血
There's a slight hypoperfusion ,in the anterior cortex.
当你查了药房记录后发现了什么
What did you find when you checked the pharmacy log?
等一下 Vickers先生
Hold on, mr. Vickers.
谢谢 法官大人 很难听清
Thanks, your honor.Hard to hear.
做血凝和左心室功能测试了吗
Did you test for clotting time and lv function?
法官大人 我相信这是重要的急诊
I believe this is a medical emergency,your honor.
血凝正常 心脏泵血也没问题
His blood's normal,and his heart's ,pumping it up to the brain.
但是血液没有全部传输进去
But it's not all getting there.
有什么东西阻碍了血液流动
Something's obstructing the blood flow.
House医生 之前已通知过你,好好安排你的诊断时间
Dr. House, you were given adequate notice ,to make arrangements for your patients.
并没异物导致的高压
There's no hyper intensity to suggest ,a foreign body near the region.
没有感染和脉管畸形的迹象
And no signs of infection ,or vascular malformation.
- 在更下面的地方,- House医生 把电话挂掉
- It's lower down. ,- Dr. House, hang up.
- 腰穿没有发现肿瘤,- 现在!
- The cytology on the lp doesn't suggest a tumor. ,- Now!
等一下
Hang on a second.
每次您生气的时候,声音都会变得又高又烦人吗
Does your voice always get that high ,and annoying when you're angry?
你想要进牢房吗
Do you want to go to jail?
不 谢谢
No thank you.
送他去做选择性脊椎血管造影
Set him up for a selective vertebral angiography.
我马上就去
I'm on my way.
House医生!
Dr. House--
House 坐下
house, sit down!
为什么 我很无聊
Why?I'm bored.
我在这说什么做什么都不会有任何改变了
There's nothing I can say or do that's ,gonna make a difference here.
如果你离开这个房间,我会控告你藐视法庭
If you leave this room,,I will find you in contempt.
申请休庭
Get a recess.
你发疯了吗
Are you out of your mind?
他们说要我在那呆着,其实他们根本不喜欢我
They said they wanted me there,,but I don't think they liked me.
他的音调变高并不是因为电击的缘故
His voice isn't high because of the electrical charges.
是绝经期的另一个症状
It's another symptom of menopause.
他的身体系统不断碰上女性的问题
His system keeps getting hit by women's issues.
我们按这个路线走
So let's follow the pattern.
什么阻碍血流而且在女性体内比男性更常见
What might obstruct the blood flow ,that's more common in women than men?
导管插了么
Is the catheter in?
回法庭上去吧
go back to court.
结果出来后我们会通知你的
We'll let you know the results.
闭嘴 把他接上线
Shut up and wire him.
把胼胝体的图像置中
Center the image on the interpeduncular cistern.
固定在30帧每秒的速度播放
Keep it moving at 30 frames per second.
如果你觉得动脉狭窄
If you think the arteries are narrowing,
我们要作静态造影,不需要你也可以做
we're gonna need still shots,,which we can do without you.
问题是现在路有多宽
The problem is not how wide the road is.
有个男孩手拿橡皮滚子走在人行道上
There's a guy with a squeegee on the sidewalk
导致车辆堵塞 这就是导致阻塞的原因
flagging cars, that's what's causing the slow down.
我们找到他就找到问题在哪里
We find him,we find the problem.
他接上导管了
He's wired.
开始工作 ,正在注射染料
- Go. ,- Injecting the dye.
血液进入毛细管
Blood's in the capillaries.
在那
There.
橡皮滚子先生
Mr. Squeegee.
脊膜瘤压迫连接声带的神经
Spinal meningioma pushing on the ,nerves to the vocal chords.
造成声音的变化
Creates the voice change.
那根神经刚好在
And that nerve just happens to live right near
脊动脉的脑膜分支旁边
the meningeal branch of the vertebral artery.
阻塞了通往脑部的血流
Obstructs the blood flow to the brain.
脑子出了故障 导致错误的记忆
Brain malfunctions,creating false memories.
记忆带来爱情
Memories cause love.
爱情带来伤害
Love kills.
我们也没有完全搞砸
And we didn't completely screw up.
把以前的错误抹去的同时,也给我们带来了找到真正问题的时间
Cleaning the slate bought us time ,to find the real problem.
从另一方面来说 如果我们能做得更好,根本就不需要这时间
On the other hand,if we'd been better,,we wouldn't have needed the time.
安排他的手术,把那玩意挖出来
Schedule him for surgery.,Dig that thing out.
比起来那些假的玩意,他可以开始享受真正的苦恼了
He can start enjoying real misery ,instead of the fake stuff.
House.
House
我刚刚听说你跟wilson道歉了
I just heard that you apologized to wilson.
脱瘾反应
Detoxing.
我不知道我都说了些什么
I didn't know what I was saying.
打扰一下
Excuse me.
我得去牢房了
I have to go to jail.
你在普林斯顿大学附属医院的职位是什么
What is your position at princeton-plains boro?
行政主管兼医学院院长
Chief administrator and dean of medicine.
那么监管药房是你的责任之一?
and you're responsible for oversight of the pharmacy?
是
Yes.
对不起 打扰了
Sorry, didn't mean to interrupt.
希望你不介意我们在你缺席时开庭
I hope you don't mind that ,we continued on without you.
我道过歉了
I said I was sorry.
不必挖苦吧
There's no need to be sarcastic.
这是什么?
What is this?
是12月24日的药房出库记录
That's our prescription sign-out log ,from december 24.
那是House医生的签名吗?
Does that appear to be dr. House's signature?
- 是,- 他取的是什么?
- Yes.,- What has he signed for?
给病人larry zebalusky的羟考酮
a prescription for oxycodone in ,the name of patient larry zebalusky.
- 那个病人拿到药了吗? ,- 没有
- And did those pills ever reach that patient? ,- No.
- 为什么?  ,- 他已经死了
- Why?  ,- He was already dead.
House医生知道这点
And dr. House knew this.
不错
Yes.
所以...
so...
House获得这些羟考酮是非法的?
dr. House had no legal or medical basis ,for acquiring that oxycodone?
Cuddy医生?
Dr. Cuddy?
他没有拿到药
He never got the pills.
那是他的签名
It's his signature.
记录的管理也很严格
The log is strictly controlled.
House是按方抓药了,但是没有拿到药
Dr. House did pick up a prescription,,but it wasn't for oxycodone.
羟考酮
It says oxycodone.
- 你作证时提到过-- ,- 我知道 但那不是羟考酮
- You testified it was-- ,- I know.But it wasn't oxycodone.
Wilson医生提醒我了
Dr. Wilson informed me that dr.House already tried
House医生想通过这种方式偷止痛药
to steal the pain medication of this patient,
所以我知道
which made clear to me that dr. House was in
House医生已经陷入几近绝望的境地
a particularly vulnerable and desperate state.
于是我去药房把药换了
So I went to the pharmacy and I swapped bottles.
House拿到的只是一瓶安慰剂
Dr. House only got a bottle with placebos.
我明白你想保护同事的冲动
I understand your impulse to ,protect a valued colleague.
我有存货清单表
I have it right here on the inventory report
法官大人 她在撒谎,那个报表明显是她伪造的
your honor, she's lyinG.,She's obviously forged that report.
按照这个证据...
In light of this evidence...
如果是真的 为什么不早点拿出来?
if this is real, why didn't she mention it earlier?
我提议驳回诉讼
I move to dismiss this case.
还有其他证据 法官大人
There is other evidence,your honor.
大家安静 坐下
Everyone shut up and sit down.
Cuddy医生 为什么你现在才提呈证据?
Dr. Cuddy, why are you only now ,coming forward with this?
我从没想过会走到这一步
I guess I never expected it to go this far.
证人可以离开了
The witness is excused.
法官大人 你不能相信--
Your honor, you can't serisly believe--
House医生 请起立
dr. House, please stand.
我怀疑你上司--
My suspicion is your boss--
我怀疑你是否应该拥有这样的好朋友
my suspicion is you have better friends ,than you deserve.
法律面前人人平等
Rules and laws apply to everyone.
你并不如自己想的那般特殊
You are not as special as you think.
但Tritter探长使你特殊化了
But detective tritter chose to make you so.
探长 我不清楚事情的经过
Detective,I don't know exactly what's going on here,
但是我确定这个人无意贩卖可卡因
but I am sure that this man is ,not flooding the streets with cocaine.
我还可以确定
I'm also certain that,knowing dr. House,
他一定是做了什么惹火你的事情
he must've done something to set you off.
但你的工作就是这样
But you're gonna have to live with it.
有了Cuddy医生的证据,我不会将案子交给陪审团
Given dr. Cuddy's testimony,I'm not going to ,allow this to proceed to jury.
本案驳回
Case dismissed.
本庭解散
Court is adjourned.
house医生 因你擅自退席,仍然有藐视法庭罪
Dr house, you're still guilty of ,contempt for that little walkout earlier.
你被处以一晚的监禁
You'll be spending the night in jail,
然后去康复中心治疗
and after that, you're going right back to your rehab.
Bailiff 带走House
Bailiff, take dr. House into custody.
House医生
Dr. House.
我要提防黑暗中的你吗?
So should I be looking for you in the shadows?
排气管逆火的时候都要趴下?
Flinch every time a car backfires?
祝你好运
Good luck.
希望是我错了
I hope i'm wrong about you.
我们发现了脑膜瘤
we got the meningioma.
你的大脑应该可以重新产生记忆了
Your brain should start generating ,real memories again.
我出院后怎么办?
What do I do when I get out?
你有爱你的人
You have people who love you.
他们会照顾你
They'll take care of you.
重新开始
You start over.
很惊讶你没有用勺子挖地道
surprised to see you're not spooning ,your way through the walls.
你觉得怎样?
So, what do you say?
不如申请一次配偶探视庆祝一下?
How about a conjugal visit to celebrate?
没什么好庆祝的 house
There's nothing to celebrate, house.
你让我作了伪证
You made me perjure myself.
伪造证据
Fabricate evidence.
你把连累了身边的每一个人
You make everyone around you worse for being there.
唯一的光明一面是,现在你得听我的
The only bright spot is that ,now I own your ass.
从康复中心出来后,你的接诊量要翻一倍
When you get out of rehab,you're gonna be pulling double clinic duty,
给学生带教 帮我找投资人
giving lectures to students helping me find donors,
我说什么你都得干
and pretty much anything else I ask.
听明白了吗?
You got it?
你的丁丙诺啡
Your buprenorphine.
你从药房拿的还是伏地魔那里?
You get these from the pharmacy of from voldemort?
伏地魔那 怎么 有什么区别--
Voldemort.Why, what difference does it--
那是维柯丁
That's vicodin.
他一直偷给你维柯丁
He's been slipping you vicodin?
不是!
No!
他那样会丢了那份工资微薄的饭碗
He'd be risking his minimum wage job to do that.
一直都是这样?
The whole time?
我的超然意志说可以这样
My higher power said it was okay.
什么都没变?
Nothing's changed?
什么都没变
Nothing's changed.
那个道歉
The apology.
不需道歉计划也可成功
You didn't need to do that to make this work.
你觉得是真就是真
Believe what you want.
晚安 house
Good night, house.
明天见
I'll see you tomorrow.
晚安 wilson
Good night, wilson.